{
    "id": "8258e5fb1f164cbd8802a8afc0464965",
    "title": "General Grammar Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The actor’s individuality …………………….. him interesting.",
            "description": "We use the simple present tense to talk about facts.",
            "answers": [
                "makes",
                "is making",
                "make"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Both men were ………………………. inebriated to drive.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "so",
                "too",
                "very"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The man was so inert …………………… he seemed dead.",
            "description": "Note the pattern so ..that.",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "for",
                "because"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Blame your inertia ……………………….. the hot weather.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "on",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The crew felt unsafe …………………….. an inexperienced pilot.",
            "description": "We use the preposition with after safe and unsafe.",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "by",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Many men were infatuated ………………………. the beautiful young widow.",
            "description": "We use the preposition with after infatuate. ",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "with",
                "by"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Brass is inferior ………………………. gold.",
            "description": "We use the preposition to after inferior and superior.",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "than",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The police must inform the prisoner ………………………….. his legal rights.",
            "description": "We use the preposition of after inform.",
            "answers": [
                "about",
                "of",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Information ……………………. witchcraft can be found at the library.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "over",
                "on",
                "about"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Children are more …………………………. than adults.",
            "description": "Ingenuous means frank, open and naive.",
            "answers": [
                "ingenuous",
                "ingenious"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Smart phones are ……………………… devices.",
            "description": "Ingenious means clever or imaginative.",
            "answers": [
                "ingenious",
                "ingenous",
                "ingenuous"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Mozart had an innate genius ……………………… music.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "for",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}